wealthinsideralliance.com 2012-12-26

# Wealth Insider Alliance | Privacy Policy

Website content is for informational purposes. Communications contained herein shall not constitute offers to solicit, sell, offer or purchase securities, futures, options, currencies (spot or otherwise) or any other instruments of a financial nature. Not suitable for all investors.

Trade involves risk, and may result in financial loss. Under no circumstances does Wealth Insider Alliance guarantee results of any kind, beneficial, detrimental or otherwise. Recommendations and/or issues are neither endorsed nor guaranteed by Wealth Insider Alliance.

All content displayed is strictly of informational nature, and is not suggested or intended to replace skilled research, advice or guidance from licensed investors or otherwise. Not responsible for broker errors. This is not investment advice. Content reserved for informative purposes only.

This is not an offer to buy or sell stock. Any investment questions should be directed to qualified, licensed, professional financial experts from both private and governmental sources.

Government-Mandated Risk Disclosure Disclaimer: U.S. Government Required Disclaimer - Commodity Futures Trading Commission.

Options, Forex and Futures trading involves potential for both major and minor rewards and/or risks. Those willing to accept these risks agree to accept any and all related risks and/or benefits. If the loss is unaffordable, do not use your money for trade. Profit is never assured for any account; contents of this website do not imply or represent otherwise. Any trading system’s performance history, methodology or data analysis does not indicate results of any kind, either pending or previously.

All performance results, hypothetical and/or otherwise are speculative, limited and unrelated to those from other accounts or individuals. Profits and losses are inherently unique, and should never be expected to meet or match those of any other account. Differences should be expected. Results achieved by other programs and/or accounts are neither implied nor guaranteed. Hypothetical trading does not account for financial risk impact, accountability and penalties. Hypothetical performance results are not implied, and should not be expected to occur. Any and all adverse results and effects should be considered. Success is neither implied nor guaranteed.

Wealth Insider Alliance (“WIA” or “we” or “us”) is not a registered investment adviser. We do not and will not provide personalized investment advice. We publish opinionated information about companies that we believe our subscribers may be interested in.

This site contains “forward looking statements,” inside the definition of Section 27A of the Securities Act of 1933 and Section 21B of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934. Statements that express or involve discussions with respect to predictions, goals, expectations, beliefs, plans, projections, objectives, assumptions or future events or performance are not statements of historical fact, and may be “forward looking statements.” Such statements are based on projections, estimates and expectations at the time the statements are made, and may involve risks which could cause actual results to differ than those anticipated.

Wealth Insider Alliance and its officers, directors, partners, affiliates, contributors, consultants or employees may hold positions in securities mentioned on the Wealth Insider Alliance website. We will not initiate a position in any stock recommended for one (1) business day before our original recommendations, and one (1) day following subsequent recommendations.

In order to reduce the risk of too many traders possibly influencing the market by attempting identical trades, Wealth Insider Alliance limits the number of subscribers in any one service. Once the limit is reached, WIA may create a clone site using the same guidelines, strategies and policies. Subscribers to clone sites will receive information unique to each service, respectfully.

Last Updated: October 28, 2009

This site is owned and operated by Wealth Insider Alliance LLC. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At WealthInsiderAlliance we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

INFORMATION Wealth Insider Alliance GATHERS AND TRACKS

Wealth Insider Alliance gathers two types of information about users:

• Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive information via email, our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys.

• Information Wealth Insider Alliance gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to visitors' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does Wealth Insider Alliance divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

Wealth Insider Alliance Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:

Optional Voluntary Information  
We offer the following services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

1\. Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)  
We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Wealth Insider Alliance gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

2\. Message boards/forums policy  
Users of the site's Message Boards and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.

3\. "E-mail this to a friend" policy  
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

4\. Polling  
We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Wealth Insider Alliance may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

5\. Surveys  
Wealth Insider Alliance may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

6\. Subscriptions  
On some of our sites, we offer paid subscriptions to users who wish to voluntarily subscribe. All personal information is protected with data encryption, firewalls and passwords. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

Children  
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

Usage tracking  
Wealth Insider Alliance tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Wealth Insider Alliance does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).  
Wealth Insider Alliance sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

Cookies  
We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Wealth Insider Alliance uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.

Privacy Policy Use  
How the information you gather is used if relevant.

USE OF INFORMATION  
Wealth Insider Alliance uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic emails and newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Wealth Insider Alliance never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

Wealth Insider Alliance creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

SHARING OF INFORMATION  
Wealth Insider Alliance uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

SECURITY  
Wealth Insider Alliance operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

OPT-OUT POLICY  
We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:  
• Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.  
• Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users.

YOUR CONSENT  
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Wealth Insider Alliance LLC. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
